and idols
The third one is ?
I love to sleep.
What's the third?
Sleep
Yes, I do.
I love to sleep.
And once I fall asleep, I don't wake up without an alarm.
Is that true?
I slept 17 hours the other night.
That's a little intense, isn't it?
And your aunt here.
Great! How many hours was it?
Some people sleep for two days straight.
In the car.
17 hours is good.
That's a good record.
Did you wake yourself up?
He woke me up.
You're good if you don't get woken up.
Mm-hmm.
Well, uh, uh, yeah, but that's the longest you've ever done that, right?
It's the longest I've ever been up.
When I woke up at 17 hours.
What, are you thirsty or something?
My throat was parched.
My head hurt.
My body ached. My whole body ached.
But you have to sleep normally, right?
Yes, sir.
I know you have to take care of your skin, but...
But you can't sleep when you're doing this job, right?
I find a gap and sleep in it.
What do you mean?
For example, once...
I sleep during transportation, during hair and makeup, and in the car when I'm going home.
After I get home, I improvise and sleep until the last minute.
By the way, do you wake up when the alarm goes off?
I can't.
You can't wake up?
I'm the type of person who doesn't hear the alarm.
I don't sleep so soundly that I don't even notice it.
That's great! You have good qualities!
But you're still able to get up for work.
What?
For work?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm also a client of the office. It's fine. It's funny.
I love it when they're funny.
I'm still safe for work.
Safe?
It's just...
When you're working, when you're giving lessons?
And when you're giving lessons...
Lessons are work, right?
But, like, when I don't have any plans after work and I'm just going home...
I've overslept a bit on those occasions.
No, no, no, it's fine.
In the past, everyone who made it big loved to sleep in.
Don't worry about it.
As long as you're on time for work.
I don't care if they sleep 20 hours on their days off.
Is that a long time ago?
Since I was a little girl.
I see.
That's important.
I couldn't sleep...
But, you know, as this job goes on and on, you're going to have trouble sleeping, aren't you?
Will your body become accustomed to the entertainment industry?
I'd like to get used to it.
I'd like to get used to it, but...
I'd like to sleep five hours.
You want to sleep for five hours?
Then, if Fujii and the others suddenly decided to do something for 24 hours, there would be a lot of trouble.
Yes, I'll be a bit nihilistic by the end.
Emptiness! That's a good word!
Nakamura-san's instruction manual says, "Let me sleep.
You might be better off in this job if you come here and try your best to be cute until you get out.
This program was provided by Mucha-san, Nakamura-san's guess Goodwill-san, my great, great favorite Naruo-san, Kadoka-san, and Tomoki-san.
Thank you very much.